[Music]
um
but you think you spend the same amount
of time in choosing a care provider or
doctor or at least a place where you
will deliver pandering
[Music]
foreign
that is
this custom was created that you have to
go to a mother's place to deliver but
eat papadilla and see wonderful
mother-in-laws and beyond that i've seen
wonderful husbands who support the
ladies mommies throughout the
neighborhood
foreign
connect with the doctor or the care
provider you can't have a peaceful
delivery either
so in what way
information what we do in my birth place
i'm going to share with you so that is
a vegetable please choose a proper care
provider and also a good hospital please
don't choose a hospital for the namesake
you know liking the porsche things are
very good and you know and the cheaper
[Music]
it is an overall rebirth for you and
your family into the municipal vegetable
invest your time and that when you go to
a doctor you should feel that emotional
connect and comfort with that person
again
the hesitancy is
you know something might
[Music]
about all the
this minute this is going to happen
[Music]
you should always have a clear and
clarity mind to understand
is what you need to choose
that is what is called as an informative
decision informed
[Music]
[Laughter]
but i will always stand by your decision
the mother also feels very very
comfortable the next thing is we should
not hurry up during pregnancy or labor
we will end up an unnecessary
um
[Music]
we should give at most a time during
your first birthing so that your second
and subsequent birthing is very easy so
when things are normal let's stick on to
the nature to take up its course but
when things are not going wrong are the
proper communications
spend enough time with your care
provider and they
think about before taking a decision it
is your life your baby's life
the cartilage
important and then we spend so much time
going around shops for non-living things
be responsible it's your kid and you're
bringing a beautiful life which is going
to live for another 60 70 years so i'm
the life
so i want you to be all very responsible
take care of yourself and take care of
your baby take charge of your body as
well as your baby's life it's you who
designs all these things
take care in whatever way i can help you
with definitely a delay for you
all the